為什麼比特幣突然就在一瞬間暴漲呢?
這已經不是光看盤就可以理解的
BlackRock貝萊德的分析師跟執行長
最近又跳出來力挺比特幣
而且國際上有一個非常黑暗的故事走向
可能剛剛被移除了
如果你有任何比特幣
或者是市場上有任何投資標的
我們極佳挖出來的資訊
你可能真的會有興趣
- Over 80%
- 4 out of 5 millennial millionaires
- In the United States own crypto
- Got the whole crypto world going wild
- Honey but Jane
- She's the queen of the game
- Stacking crypto like it's her claim to fame
- If you want success then take a look away
Hello 我是Bonnie
全世界最大的資產管理公司貝萊德
他管理世界上10.5兆美元的資產
他們剛剛開了一次2024年的
第三季度的收益會議
執行長Larry Fink喊話
看好比特幣加密貨幣跟以太幣
- The role of Ethereum as a blockchain can grow dramatically
so if we can create more acceptability, more transparency, more analytics related to these assets,
then it will be expanded.
but I truly don't believe it's a function of regulation, of more regulation, less regulation.
I think it's a function of liquidity, transparency, and then through that process, no different than when you-
- You know, years ago when we started the mortgage market, years ago when the high yield market started off very slow,
- But it built as we build better analytics and data, and then through better analytics and data, more acceptance, and a broadening of the market.
- And I truly believe we will see a broadening of the market of these digital assets.
- 10月7日到11日的這一週,美國比特幣現貨ETF近流入3億多美元.
- And you also have a beautiful market market.
最强的呢就是贝莱德 BlackRock的ETF
IBIT
这个时候你可能会惊觉喔
在比特币跌的时候大多数人都不敢买
觉得会跌更多
但它一开始涨呢
跟你抢着买的就是这种等级的机构
我们每次一有国际的大消息
就会用最快速的速度把整理好的资讯交给你
很多人在加密货币航行的这个旅途上
可能会遇到的问题呢
好奇啊 疑问啊
频道很多都聊过
那如果我不会
我就会把行业里面最厉害的人邀请来聊
让你不错过任何起风的好机会啊
所以记得要订阅频道
我相信使用的资讯货币
会变得世界上更多的真实
有关联络的社会
有关联络的谈论
他们应该如何认为资讯货币
什么类型资讯货币
我们相信
比特币是资讯货币
它是一个选择
其他资讯货币
像金钱
Larry Fink说他在跟全世界对话的时候
不知道有没有让你眼睛一亮了
因为这么有话语权的机构
去跟其他机构对话
告诉其他机构要怎么样去看数位资产
贝莱德自己呢
也有比特币以太币的现货ETF
所以你觉得他们会怎么样建议人家吗
其实这件事情的答案呢
已经不是秘密了
因为10月初
巴西有一场很大的数位资产会议
叫做Digital Assets Conference
贝莱德的J Jacobs
已经把答案好像跟大家说了
We're still just at the starting point for digital assets
We've still just started to make
这些资产会更加充足的投资者
和世界各地的资产
所以很多人在这里
我认为你的旅程可能已经开始了
数年代的资产
但认为外面的大多数位资产
我们仍然在第一次的资产
J Jacobs说他作为这个BlackRock
数位投资部门的负责人
他的工作呢就是花很多时间去想说
哦未来有什么东西会影响世界吗
什么东西会影响社会会
会影响经济
当然最重要的是什么会影响他们的投资组合
有没有什么颠覆性的科技啊
是不是有颠覆性的社会变革
也是他们考虑的重点
But what we found with blockchain and digital assets
is that in some ways
this is one of the fastest growing technologies
we've seen in the last few years
on the right hand side of the chart
you can see our adoption curve
this is just looking at how quickly
certain assets are adopted by society
and you can see that blockchain and digital assets
are being adopted faster than major revolutions before it
whether that's the internet or whether that's cell phones
and there's a couple of reasons for this
the first reason is just we're living in a more digital economy than ever before
if we're consuming things online streaming videos
playing video games buying digital content
it makes sense to have digitally native assets to conduct those transactions
secondly and importantly in a year like this year
where over half the world's population is voting for new leadership
not just the elections in the United States
in Mexico, in India, in the European Union
we're seeing more geopolitical risk than before
and in fact declining trust in institutions
whether that's trust in government institutions
for maintaining peace and order
whether that's trust in central banks
in terms of keeping inflation under control
more distrust has exacerbated the need for a global monetary alternative
the third we're seeing is demographic changes
the rise of the millennial and Gen Z generation
millennials at least in the United States
are set to inherit trillions of dollars
are entering peak earnings years in their work
and are increasingly playing an important role in the economy
and millennials are very different from previous generations
because they we me were the first generation to be digitally native
growing up with the internet growing up with computers
we understand digital better than previous generations
and that means we're more likely to adopt digital currencies
Jey说对于BlackRock來說
一个很重要的指標是
数位资产的基础设施
到底成熟了没有
他們看好这个几十亿美元的资金
进入区块链的风险投资
还有这个私募股权
也看到了监管环境变好
还有很多很有才华的人
离开了传统金融
投身到DeFi去中心化金融裡面
但他认为我们还处在这个币圈的非常早期
但这不是要叫大家闭着眼睛充
因为比特币呢
它还是一个风险资产
虽然大部分的年份
比特币浅蓝色的这个部分
都是各种资产类别里面表现最好的
但是少数市场比较不好的年份
比特币也可以是表现最烂的资产标底
不过如果要算整体长期来说呢
比特币的回报它还是最高的
接下来这一段可能会回答到贝莱德
到底要怎么建议其他的机构配置比特币
I'll start by showing you just kind of a global portfolio
your classic 60-40, 60% acqui, 40% bonds portfolio
with just little slivers to Bitcoin
1% allocated to Bitcoin
coming from the equity part of your portfolio
or 3% of Bitcoin
and we found a couple things
one is looking backwards
Bitcoin has performed very well over the long term
it increased the returns of portfolios
we also found Bitcoin is a risky asset
it increased the volatility of portfolios
but interestingly the return of portfolios
increased more than the risk
and what this is really highlighting
is the diversification property of Bitcoin
that because it is not very correlated to stocks and bonds
you get a little bit of benefit from it being a different type of asset in your portfolio
所以我们知道了BlackRock心里是怎么走
但下一个问题是他做得到吗
BlackRock的首席投资官说了为什么比特币有一些价格潜力
还没有发挥出来
Then there's this bigger category that I would consider asset owners
like pensions and endowments
where there's actually a fair amount of plumbing
still to unlock their ability to buy Bitcoin
it could be again
what is the financial position of the fund
does it make sense to have a Bitcoin allocation
and if the answer is yes
does state law permit the pension fund to buy Bitcoin ETPs
do their investment guidelines
does their board and these things take a longer period of time
so all of those steps kind of
and this is a process that is underway
but it will be a
like we are in early like act one of this play
除了BlackRock最近好像吃了定心碗
然后强力地替比特币持有者狂打鸡血之外
其实还有一个国际上面超大的风险
可能稍微被解除啦
10月1号
这个伊朗不是有200颗飛弹攻击以色列吗
那以色列就说伊朗必须要付出代价
这就让全世界的市场都超紧张的
If I were in those shoes
I'd be thinking about other alternatives than striking oil fields
原因是因为呢
伊朗它是全世界第七大的产油国
如果以色列去炸伊朗的油田
那光是这件事情呢
就可能让国际的原油价格冲破
100美金一桶
或者是说如果冲突升级了
然后伊朗挡住了荷莫兹海峡
那可能立刻瞬间呢
就引发一场史无前例的金融危机
啊ちょっと待って等一下
这个荷莫兹海峡是什么
为什么这么重要
最悲惨的情况是
如果伊朗的攻击
伊朗的攻击以防止
或是可能尽量阻止
Halmuz的沙拉
会有更加重大影响
因为那是在
20%的世界的货源货源
都迅速通过
荷莫兹海峡的位置是伊朗跟阿曼中间
他把中东的产油国跟世界各地
最主要的这些市场连接起来
好像就是石油的大动脉
2022年的数据说呢
这里的这个运输量啊
平均每一天大概是2100万桶
占了全球原油的贸易量21%
那以色列媒体说啦
以色列可能的计划是
先攻击以色列的油田或者是石油设施
然后如果伊朗会还手打回来
那以色列的第二波攻击呢
会去锁定这个伊朗的核设施
这就让美国超紧张的啦
The White House laying down two red lines at this point
Do not attack Iranian nuclear facilities
Also do not attack Iranian oil installations
on the Persian Gulf
which could spike global oil prices
If that was to be impacted
We're talking about an oil price impact
which would be three times larger
Then the oil price shocks of the 1970s
in the wake of the Iranian revolution
and the Arab oil embargo
And now we're talking about
150 dollar plus a barrel oil
It would actually be a record global energy crisis
Already coming up on top of a quite a fragile market
in the wake of the reduction of Russian gas
over the last two years
这里说的石油禁运呢
讲的是1973年的这个石油危机
当时沙烏地阿拉伯为首的
这个阿拉伯石油输出国组织成员国啊
宣布要对这个在赎罪日战争期间呢
支持以色列的国家进行石油的禁运
第一批的目标国家呢
是加拿大、日本、荷兰、英国还有美国
之后葡萄牙跟南非呢
也被列上黑名单
那这个石油禁运的期间呢
全世界的石油价格上涨了将近300%
从每桶3块美元飙到十几块美金
那原油价格暴涨就让美国陷入了
超级严重的通膨跟经济衰退
失业率呢也爆炸性的上升啊
好那镜头拉回到现在
原本大家非常担心这同样的事件呢
会重演
但最新的消息是
美国白宫的知情人士传出来
他们说以色列的总理
已经质疑过拜登政府啦
说计划攻击的目标呢
会是伊朗的军事设施
不会针对石油或者是核设施
也就是说以色列呢
他会避免全方位的开战
我们刚刚听到了
加密货币的基础问题要被解决呢
其实监管的态度很关键吧
最近我们也看到了
阿联酋呢
给了OKX交易所
这边含一个很重要的讯息
也就是说
阿联酋它是很多加密货币公司
总部设立的地方嘛
那他们对新科技
还有加密货币是出了名的很重视
我觉得他们是蛮有元件的
因为你知道以前杜拜
是一个更没有人管的小渔村嘛
他们当时就是超级有野心的啊
建海港
投资世界上面
其中最大的两家航空公司
杜拜的Emirates
阿布达比的Etihad
对不对
搞关光盖饭店
各种发展
讲这些就是说
除了这里有钱
还有这种开疆辟土的决心
那OKX交易所拿到这个许可
也就等于可以合法交易
资产管理
还有托管加密货币资产
更重要的是呢
你可以用当地的货币
AED DIRUMS去投资
不知道看完这个影片
有没有让你打鸡血的感觉哦
留言区可以分享一下
你自己的比特币持仓呢
占了所有加密货币的多少
目前呢
是少于30%的帮我打个1
30%到60%的打个2
60%以上的帮我打个3
拜拜
谢谢你看到这里哦
欢迎用下面的连结到LINE
跟Discord群组
跟努力的大家一起讨论
我们在OKXBM派网呢
跟其他的大交易所都帮大家
争取到了最高8折20% OFF的
交易手续费减免
用下面的连结注册呢
你的交易成本就更低了
也欢迎告诉我
你接下来想要看什么
我们在币圈继续努力下一次见
拜拜
拜训